* Religions ▼

* Charts ▼

Privacy Policy
==============

published October 3, 2013 · updated June 10, 2024

ReligionFacts.com does not collect any personally-identifiable information from visitors. No part of the site requires you to register or log in, and we don't use cookies.

To understand how visitors are using our website, we use [Simple Analytics](https://www.simpleanalytics.com/), which is based in Europe and "100% privacy friendly." This service logs basic information such as how many people visited, how long they stayed, what country they're from, and what site they came from to get to ours. None of this information tells us or them who you are.

If you give us personal information, such as your e-mail address when writing us, we won't disclose this information to anyone else nor use it to send you anything but a reply.

This privacy policy covers ReligionFacts.com only.

We currently use Google AdSense advertising to support the costs of this website. Please see [their privacy policy](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites) for what data they may gather.

Article Info
------------

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Article Title | Privacy Policy |
| Date Published | October 3, 2013 |
| Last Updated | June 10, 2024 |
| Full URL | https://religionfacts.com/privacy |
| Short URL | https://rlft.co/1879 |
| MLA Citation | “Privacy Policy.” _ReligionFacts._ 3 Oct 2013, https://religionfacts.com/privacy. Accessed 20 Jun 2024. |
| Embed Link | <a href="https://religionfacts.com/privacy">Privacy Policy</a> — ReligionFacts |

© 2004-2024 [ReligionFacts](https://religionfacts.com/). All rights reserved.

ReligionFacts provides free, objective information on religion, world religions, comparative religion, and religious topics.

We are not associated with any religion or organization.

[Definitions of Religion](https://religionfacts.com/religion) · [List of Religions](https://religionfacts.com/religions) · [Big Religion Chart](https://religionfacts.com/big-religion-chart)

[About Us](https://religionfacts.com/about) · [Privacy Policy](https://religionfacts.com/privacy)
